dealdatabase.com 2002-12-08

# DealDatabase.com Policy Statement

## Privacy Statement for DealDatabase

**DealDatabase** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [DealDatabase](http://www.dealdatabase.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. _(** ELABORATE here on the purpose(s) stated above and explain here what other purposes you use the logged information for. **)_

#### Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. _(** Please elaborate on your use of cookies here.)_

#### Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors for other purposes. _(* EXPLAIN here what other purposes you use this information for. *)_

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **DealDatabase** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Special Relationships

_(** Special relationships are often very confusing, as the collection of information is often seamless to the user. Because you indicated that there are special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, content providers, business partners, cobranded sites, then these relationships must be addressed in your privacy statement. These relationships need to be clearly defined and it must be clear who owns the information, who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information. It must be clear what type of information is shared. Is only select information shared? Is the sharing of information limited to only aggregate information? **)_

#### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. _(** Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place. **)_

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
